<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<creature>
  <!--
    info - 관찰 레벨과는 관련 없는 정보들 ex)데미지, id, 이미지 소스 등
    
    observe - 관찰 정도에 따라 제공되는 정보들
              각 정보들에는 정보가 제공되는 레벨을 표기
              ex) <desc id="1" openLevel="1">"openLevel이 1일 때 이 정보가 제공됨"</desc>
              
              observe 노드 안의 level 은 관찰 단계의 갯수를 나타냄
  -->
  <info
    id ="100006"

    script="SingingMachine"
    >

    <stat>
      <horrorProb>0.1</horrorProb>
      <horrorMin>2.0</horrorMin>
      <horrorMax>2.0</horrorMax>
      <physicsDmg>3.0</physicsDmg>
      <mentalDmg>0.0</mentalDmg>
      <feelingMax>210.0</feelingMax>
      <feelingDownValue>4.0</feelingDownValue>
      <energyPointChange>-4</energyPointChange>
      <energyGenSection>
        <section bound="50" gen="-0.1125"/>
        <section bound="120" gen="0.3"/>
        <section bound="210" gen="-0.1125"/>
      </energyGenSection>
    </stat>

    <feeling max="100" downProb="0.44" downValue="1">
      <section feelingValue="50" state="good" energy="0.5"/>
      <section feelingValue="30" state="normal" energy="0.3"/>
      <section feelingValue="0" state="bad" energy="-1.3"/>
    </feeling>

    <narration action="move">
      -> #0 designated to 'Singing Machine' isolation sector.
    </narration>
    <narration action="start">
      -> [
     {Ordinary grinder maybe in front of you, but please be careful. Every Abnormality  may not have reason to exist, but have intention to exist},
      {It has an extremely powerful suction force.},
      {Music that it emits is known to be terribly beautiful.},
      {Your blood and flesh, shall we harmonize and melodize.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid1">
      -> [
      {Singing Machine’ is not in motion if anyone isn’t nearby.},
      {Until #0 enters, ‘Singing Machine’ doesn’t move in the slightest. },
      {Until #0 enters this isolation sector, ‘Singing Machine’ is nothing more than a normal machine that’s turned off.},
      {If ‘Singing Machine’ had a power switch, #0 might have been more comfortable working.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid2">
      -> [
      {#0 is working on ‘Singing Machine’ with extreme caution},
      {#0 is always cautious since ‘Singing Machine’ can be activated at any time.},
      {‘Singing Machine’ is not responding to #0 as if it is digesting prior grounds internally.}
      {#0 is working on ‘Singing Machine’ while it is not in motion }
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid3">
      -> [
      {It is simple to figure out when ‘Singing Machine’ activates; just open its lid and check how much leftover grounds are digested.},
      {#0 does not enough guts to open the lid to check ‘Singing Machine’ ‘s next activation. .},
      {-Rumor has it that any employee that has opened the lid of ‘Singing Machine’ later became sick.}
      {Actually, the insides of ‘Singing Machine’ is known to be sophisticated but no employee dares to check it with their own eyes.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="mid4">
      -> [
      {It is a lucky day for #0. ‘Singing Machine’ has not been activated.}
      {For #0, they are thankful that ‘Singing Machine’ is not active. But condolences to whichever employee is going to work there after.}
      {‘Singing Machine’ has decided to take a day off.}
      {‘Singing Machine’ is not responding as it is still finishing up what its leftover. }
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="dead">
      -> [
     {The isolation sector is full of unprecedented harmony made by ‘Singing Machine’.},
      {To generate the very best masterpiece, a sacrifice must be made. ‘Singing Machine’ is the best example of such phrase.}
      ]
    </narration>
    <narration action="panic">
      -> [
      {#0 is possessed by the timbre  of ‘Singing Machine. #0 will not listen to any command.}
      {#0 is charmed by transmundane  song of ‘Singing Machine’. #0’s mind is completely paralyzed.}
      ]
    </narration>

    <anim prefab="Unit/CreatureAnimator/machine" x="-1" y="-2"/>

    <!--<img src="Unit/creature/MatchGirl_01" x="-1" y="-1"/>-->
    <img src="Unit/dummy" x="-1" y="-1"/>
    <portrait src="Unit/Creature/Machine"/>
    <room src="Unit/creature/isolate_room"/>
    <frame src="Unit/creature/frame/MagicalGirl_frame"/>

    <graph>
      <node id="creature" x="-1.6" y="-1" type="creature"/>
      <node id="workspace" x="1.9" y="-1" type="workspace"/>

      <!--<node id="door"  x="2" y="-1" type="entry"/>-->
      <node id="outter" x="0" y="0" type="outterDoor"/>
      <node id="inner" x="2" y="-1" type="innerDoor"/>

      <!--<edge node1="workspace" node2="door" type="road" />-->
      <edge node1="workspace" node2="inner" type="road" />
      <edge node1="creature" node2="workspace" type="road" />
    </graph>
    
    <sound action="attack" src="creature/match_girl/matchgirl_attack"/>
    <sound action="enter" src="creature/match_girl/matchgirl_enter"/>
    
  </info>
  
  <observe level ="4">
    <collection>
      <codeNo openLevel ="0">O-05-30-H</codeNo>
      <portrait openLevel ="0">Unit/Creature/Machine</portrait>
     
      <size openLevel ="0">4</size>

      <weight openLevel ="0">120kg</weight>

      <name openLevel ="1">Singing Machine</name>
      <attackType openLevel ="2">Red</attackType>
        
      <creatureType openLevel ="1">THING</creatureType>

      <horrorLevel openLevel ="1">0</horrorLevel>

      <riskLevel openLevel ="2">HE</riskLevel>

      <intelligence openLevel ="1">1</intelligence>

      <physical openLevel ="2">5</physical>

      <mental openLevel ="0">0</mental>

      <specialName openLevel ="0">0</specialName>

      <specialInfo openLevel ="0">0</specialInfo>

      <aggression openLevel ="3">3</aggression>

      <gorgeous openLevel ="2">1</gorgeous>
      
      <rejectWork openLevel ="0"></rejectWork>
      
      <preferWork openLevel ="0">
                
      </preferWork>
      <solution openLevel ="0">0</solution>
      
    </collection>
    
    <desc id="1" openLevel="0">
    -> [
        {The machine takes the shape of a long cylinder.}
       ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="2" openLevel="1">
     -> [
        {By the look of it, it may look like a simple grinder but the existence of the thing’s own ‘will’ fills the criteria of Abnormality}
       ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="3" openLevel="2">
    -> [
        {When approached (extra experiments are needed to determine how many meters the perimeter actually is) or touched, the Abnormality ‘operates’ and with a strong suctioning power, pulls in a nearby subject inside its body. } 
        ]
    </desc>

    <desc id="4" openLevel="3">
    -> [
        {Afterwards, the body’s fan shuts  and the Abnormality works on the task. The task takes approximately 5 minutes.}
       ]
    </desc>

      <desc id="5" openLevel="4">
    -> [
        {After a few experiments, we have concluded that the Abnormality desires the result of ‘music’ from this interaction. Employees are needed to fulfill that specific need every once in a while in order to prevent the creature’s stress levels from rising.}
       ]
    </desc>


    <record openLevel="1">
     -> [
        (Excerpt from Interview Log)
        Employee M2543 : “I was supposed to be sent in alone. The Abnormality looked rather unassuming. Something like a machine used in a factory, as it didn’t even react to anything. But that day, [Redacted] insisted that we had to go there. The ‘Pale Horse’ had responded to something specifically that he had said, he repeated that a lot. I didn’t think ‘Pale Horse’ was thinking about [Redacted] when it responded. Most of the Abnormalities that I take care of are tame. Also, I’m very lucky. I thought that day would be the same. (Omitted)}
        ]
    </record>

    <record openLevel="2">
    ->[
       {[Redacted] closely observed the Abnormality. I just wanted to write the report quickly and get out, but he was thinking differently. He was sure; there wouldn’t be an Abnormality that doesn’t have special powers. I warned him not to get too close, but [Redacted] took one step closer. And suddenly, the thing came to life, opened its lid and swallowed him whole. Literally swallowed him.}
       ]
    </record>

    <record openLevel="3">
     -> [
        {The lid closed and a loud noise came from the inside of the creature, there was no way of knowing what was happening, but I was too terrified to do anything. (Omitted)
        }
        ]
    </record>

      <record openLevel="4">
     -> [
          {In the dark, I realized that the thing was playing an instrument. By crushing and cutting [Redacted]’s body, it was creating a melody. As I was contemplating my horrific realizations, the lid opened again. Bits and pieces of [Redacted] were in there. So little that you had to wonder as to what happened to the rest. (Omitted)
          }
        ]
        [
          {Excerpt from Incident Log
          XXXX XXth, there was a disappearing incident of employee M1840. 2 days later on the XXth, part of the body was found inside the ‘Singing Machine’. DNA analysis has found the corpse to be of employee M1840. Employee M1840 was a new hire who had worked in the company for only 3 months, the employee had no record of an assignment with the Abnormality. The employee assigned to the ‘Singing Machine’, [Redacted] was the suspect. After an extensive investigation, [Redacted] confessed to the crime. 

          “I know it’s crazy, but I had to hear that music again. It wouldn’t get out of my head for months. I performed all kinds of experiments. When the machine takes in a cat, it plays for 1 minute. A large dog, 2 minutes and 30 seconds, [Redacted] music came from it. But nothing was like a human’s music. It might sound ridiculous but I feel satisfied after having heard it once more.”
          }
        ]
    </record>
    
  </observe>
</creature>